welcome to yet another episode of
wellness 360 at home
brought to you by icy haciendo bad well
hum last little cool
tried echo or Aki ravage me building
Agathe I'm Sean who stood in my acne
vodkas practice chia-chu hamari guest
name October taiga and I'm sure all be
fit or happy oogie oogie again we were
two very easy the aura hamari pakki or
fulness or cushion jahar / it's all
about becoming perfect and the best
version of who you are
welcome again the most interesting
episodes ever and here it is with
something more charming
this is wellness 360 at home brought to
you by ICICI Lombard
my name is Matilda Bosnia and today
we're here with the most important
factor of wellness is it nutrition is it
laughter yoga meditation workout kana
picanha haha get ahead but it's kill sot
sot a core bought the important aspect
of that
who the heck cybersecurity car yeah
Nicki aqua transaction Jodi her phone
kid whare yeah laptop kid wat da da da
David Ghidorah is underway or skip
behind since Macau is full present
clinically an ahmadi Bhishma a valet
it sa guest this is Pattaya Pattaya
so please welcome well he is a
well-known cyber crime investigator of
cyber security and data privacy
consultant he has been instrumental in
investigating very high-profile
cybercrime cases for the law enforcement
agencies and corporates he is the
founder director of beef for web spam a
security it is key areas to pay to dress
include cyber crime investigations
protection of sensitive personal data
and dark web his views on training cyber
crimes have been published by many media
houses and he has debated on national
television channels such as NDTV CNBC C
news mirror
and many others to highlight the dangers
in cyberspace that we all keep asking
ourselves he has also played the role of
the dual life
cyber crime investigator in MTV's
award-winning reality show called as the
MTB troll police the very delighted very
happy to welcome here at the Wellness
360 at home the one and only British
Hachiya with us right now
heritage good evening welcome to the
Wellness 360 how are you doing this
evening
very well mitten very happy to see that
energy in you even as this ah it's the
only thing that's keeping me going with
the Wellness coming along you know I'm
really really happy that it's coming to
us and it's helping us nurture our date
but today I let me tell you it's a very
interesting day for me and for those
millions of people who always have this
question about TM transaction Caray he
may agree or I think of wellness starts
from being at a comfortable side make it
fit about what money is going way so we
have very delighted to have you and
little section begin and let's let's all
learn today how to save AVI when it
comes to cybersecurity and more so it's
all to you and let the session of
wellness 360 at home begin now
Thank You Martin so azmuth and rightly
says it's all about the wellness so here
we are with a digital wellness you know
so let's let's start with it of course
the first position that would be coming
into your mind is zoom okay we are on
bloom and you know many people like
parents and teachers are on zoom and all
and children are Zoom Zoom is perfectly
fine you know as I always say that if
you want to change your clothes you're
not going to go into the biasing and
change your clothes right and then you
cannot complain the world is watching so
given some security settings that are
there and zoom if you enable those
security settings you're safe to go so
you don't have to worry about it in fact
yesterday we came to know that even
Microsoft team which is again a very
popular platform they were
vulnerabilities that over there also so
as far as its technology it can be
hacked so so but then don't take so much
of tension so mistake to go second break
do the Wi-Fi now you know now we are
working from home all the routers are on
that's what I fight fires guns on each
end we have a well I see people coming
up you know some hot the fellow coming
and putting up the Wi-Fi router but
please understand we need to ask
ourselves it really changed the deal
fault II's if we change the default
username or password if it allows us to
change the username also so many of
these Wi-Fi routers they have a default
IP which I generally changed they have a
default user name which certain
companies allow me to change and the
password definitely can be changed so
please change that and I'm not talking
about the the passwords of the SSID
which you need when you start your
device and you know you select your name
like okay this is of the method and then
you put your password no I'm talking
about
so that is required get into the router
and kabuto settings so please ensure
that you are taking care of those things
now with the lockdown happening and all
that is you know the fraud are
inevitable and one of those cause I
would say is the key of I see fraud has
been happening since quite a lot of long
time but off lately it has just
increased and here is what you get a
message that you know I'm from this
particular digital app and your kyc has
expired and because of that you would be
able to use your digital wallet and they
give a particular number so something
like okay the commands it has come from
let's say for example AT&T I see you
know they've modified it a little bit
and oh you know you are worried because
most of the payments are happening
digitally whether this you know your
mind cooking grocery or wherever you're
going to get scared like it now to
accept the cash so you would want to do
that and so you don't want to pay them
to be blocked for your digital wallet to
be blocked so you call them up and the
moment you call them up they are going
to encroach into curtain conversation
and which may lead you to revealing your
PIN or maybe of you installing a
software such as any desk or TeamViewer
onto your phone and the moment you start
entering all your details such as a
although you Kevin they are able to see
each and everything what you're doing so
please be very careful about this do not
follow such messages if at all there is
an issue in your app for example kyc
related open your app the app tells you
what exactly you have produced step by
step another fraud I would want to
quickly touch upon is let's say you're
expecting of Korea and when you are
expecting the video and you know you
suddenly get a call that I am calling
from this particular Korean company and
the parcel is there but you need to make
some payment and you know you would want
to ask you why I need to make a payment
it's of detail thing they would say no
we need to just inform because it's
lockdown and they'll give you all
rubbish excuses
they will then kind of like send your
form the form will look exactly like of
a puja zombie of course Google from any
intelligent person will say no system
but no many people have you
don't call in three two visits and there
they are certain questions you answer
them over there you also give up in your
UPI pin moment you give your UPI pin to
enter PIN for you back and then they say
okay you must have got a food the poor
starts with the word activist and then
few like strings of characters and
alphabets are there and they are over so
moments you have done all that you lose
a lot of money yesterday itself somebody
some poor fellow lost twenty thousand
rupees so please be careful about any
such frauds that are happening now the
government recently announced that there
is going to be is like you know the
income tax refunds are going to be
expedited and because of that you mind
me also receiving a lot of nails
now the mains will be showing that these
are from income tax department or from
the Ministry of Finance and they're not
these they will be an attachment over
there and it would say ok this much
money has been deposited
kindly chakki attachment all this money
has also been deducted kinda check the
attachment the moment you you know
because most of you are now working from
home I'm assuming you're definitely
using your desktop for the laptop
moments you click over there am as well
get in
Stolz on your laptop or a desktop and
you're not even aware about it so again
these could be spyware this could be any
sort of malware so please for all those
people working from home please ensure
that you maintain the wellness even of
your system okay so we're talking about
the 360 wellness or the wellness or the
devices also come under this particular
thing and then now when we are anyway
talking about the devices even sure that
you know you don't share these devices
with your fam be like with children or
with your spouse or anybody it's a not a
flat top or if it's work-related please
ensure that is the use of work only and
whatever that's the reason you things do
not click on any fishing related emails
like the thing I told you about the
income tax thing a new one that is
coming up is or that is already doing
round it is what we called as a health
emergency scan or rather family
emergency scam now here what happens is
you get a mail from a friend of yours
saying that either he or the spouse I
mean someone from his family has been
hospitalized and there is some reason
where he's not able to call you and all
that but he needs fund because of person
of cotrona and you know the bills are
mounting and he's in a different country
or maybe even the same country in a
different state and you know you would
want to just transfer money yes people
have done that I'm sure you would have a
question
that's the widened it all up or why
didn't he whatsapp I would say if please
not doesn't anything you can do that
firstly it's a scam because you know if
anything like this happens we at least
in India we call up people we don't
email so please be very very careful
about this particular term which is
against rising we were also coming back
to the devices you know we spoke about
the phishing emails also please ensure
that you have a password on your desktop
so that even if you have to move out of
the room
close the lid please close to the three
and so that when you start it again
again there is a passwords over there
the reason being is if somebody from the
family or someone else just not able to
like you know mess
that now well because you're also
dealing the trip in to take a little
data now since I've spoken over the word
data let's talk about the data pattern
now when you are in an organization when
you're in your office you know you have
systems which automatically pick up you
know backup your date stuff by the way
here the responsibilities are so we need
to make sure that all of this data which
is there you know we are securing it
please don't like try to email it to
yourself but just imagine what a URI
email gets had some three days now so we
need to be very careful about it yes you
can save it another different folder and
pack it up somewhere on the drive but
make sure you don't use your personal
email ID in just you know your bosses
have given you certain systems wherein
you can log in and put up all the data
because we don't have much ID support
also something going wrong with the
Machine maybe we'll be able to do
without the machine without the data it
will become extremely difficult so
please make sure that the backing of
time and again another very very
important thing is your antivirus you
know we always dictate that antivirus is
there or on the desktop but has an
anti-virus been updated many of the
times we feel oh it makes a much cheaper
so we just switch it off please don't do
that mistake the contact your first line
of defense the only thing that
technically technically going to help
you technically going to protect you so
ensure that your antivirus is running
and it's a set and you know whenever
like you switch on the machine just go
and check whether the antivirus has been
updated or not it should always show the
latest date or maximum like you know a
day before like it's today's 27 it
should show okay updated in verse 26 of
April I'm also do a quick scan if you
know when you start the machine it's
nice if you can do a quick scan and this
is as far as the digital thing digital
wellness concern as well as your laptop
is concern there's a lot more but I also
understand that you may be having lots
many questions also
so hence I'm going to little parks and
trying to keep it shot um lot of
messages are coming right that we will
give you Netflix
towns and geo DD charges and all done
nothing but smile face please don't try
to click on them and you don't know even
if it's a mobile device you could be
having malware's or certain kind of like
data sweeping things running as the
background so here is something that you
really need to take care of when it
comes to now saving the data on your
devices also these very very careful
because most of the apps have access to
everything when I say everything I mean
by and large what's very important for
you gallery your SMS listicle satisfy
you the CG of the piece the contact and
many of times we save our ATM things or
use OPI pens or anything else
we are saving it to where we are saving
it in the contacts or we often also take
it like you know photographs of our
identities and then we are saving it in
the gallery but please understand many
apps have access to this coming to be
apps please make sure that you have very
limited that you really don't need so
many apps as such only the apps which
are like really used ring we need to
have them now for example some of you
might already we have ring apps of jet
air is now flying only but you really
need a uninstalled maintain you know
your phone also need a little digital
hygiene digital wellness so please
ensure that you take care of such things
password now most of the issues arise
because we use the same path so I'm not
even talking about whether the passwords
are you know weak or strong or they have
to be but I'm talking about using the
same password across all the platforms
so which means the binary extreme and
password why it's like these as you know
the same thing and work on Facebook and
work on Twitter or it can work anywhere
else also or even if not I am able to at
least or you know do a forgot password
and have it on to your email id and then
he said and that's the reason it's
extremely important we use different
passwords for different applications and
if something is
kind of a deal if you ask me yes I know
you would be surprised at how different
passwords for different applications and
you say it's a DZ yes it is so firstly
instead of the password use a passphrase
what the password computer becomes the
fastest which is just one would use a
passphrase my computer is true
that's a passphrase Thank You firstly
use fast faces now now my computer is
slow is like simple right it can be
hacking is real
just something in your own mother tongue
you know if hinge means your mother
tongue you can just write with the
Peloponnese no Alec read a Sunday you
know Alex Pettyfer Sundays become that
and then you use a hashtag and skip a
does do G major so polyphony for some
day I have send email becomes my
password for Gmail I look so nice %
their hash tag FB becomes for Facebook
and so on of course you need to make
pile up Matheny capital and then at the
rate add some number or something like
that
Cindy sounds easy so now you know
polyphony welcome here by the way I
don't like that much polyphony for some
hair it becomes with the first part and
that is means if you remember the back
so only after remember o is for my and
toward it would be hashtag DOB
microfarad our hashtag ICICI that that
makes it easy for you to remember and
you also have a complicated password a
very strong password two-factor
authentication is extremely important
because even if I get it the strong
password of yours you know the fancy in
your mother tongue and everything I can
still get into it yes that is exactly
what smells like aiways do they can like
you know record whatever you're doing
there are key lovers which end of all
your keystrokes so but one thing what
they can do is for the two-factor
authentication that also possible but
then you know now we are getting like
too much of in the hacker mode I don't
want to get into that let's just I
understand that the proof factor so even
if I know your gmail password it will
ask you for one more port it should come
on your mobile when an SMS or to a flash
message something like that
so two-factor authentication for
the applications that you use whether
it's Facebook whether the gene male
whether it's you know it even if it's
something related something pleasing
sure that is there so here I think I
spoke over too many things which I felt
was relevant so what I would want to do
is now within if I can have you back and
I understand that a lot many questions
and should we take up some questions me
well well well I must say that was
really really interesting dish III have
so many questions personally I'm sure
many others also have questions ever
asked you but I just wanna start the Q&A
and of course everybody is watching us
live on Facebook Instagram a course in
this portal so let's start with this
portal you mentioned about zoom and
there were this big news I think the
goof of that the CEO of zoom did was the
big problem that everybody understood
that he did say out in the public that
you know what yes we are getting into
account details the people so good that
you clear this in the air that zoom is
safe we can use it it's been existing
for the last eight years it's only now
that majority of Indians have come
across this so thank you for clearing
this air flow to people but also you
know we don't know what whatsapp being
encrypted completely what's your take on
this is well except completely safe so
let's understand one thing what's up
what do you mean by end-to-end
encryption so let's say I have tied a
particular tape okay
when this is in transit means when it
goes from my device to your device for
that particular period of time its
interface when it is on my device it
stays there when it is on your device it
stays there a you know have you seen how
you get those notification you know you
have notification managers also so which
means they are able to read right if you
install any notification app you know
the cat you know they just like nice
categorize all the notifications either
your cache modifications these are your
SMS relative run notifications so which
means any app can actually be your text
messages
Soho you know it's very important if
you're going to have some kind of TV
talk with somebody and show that you
delete it immediately I like about it
and I'm just thinking on all over again
but lucky you matured out of the school
days were not 1517 anymore so any one of
those things I have a question coming in
from rahi she's asking what are the
security measures we should take while
making digital payments
I'm sure rice putting this question out
but it's a question that 80% of people
have in their mind while doing this to
payment so your answer for that okay so
when you're making the digital payment
just just make sure like you know you're
when the app is there your app also
should be like really secure so when I
was talking about two-factor
authentication let me also add that you
know there are there are things
available and if there is an actively
bill or even your phone and enables our
two-factor authentication for you so
that means a double security at the
moment your unlock your phone and then
again to open up a digital app or
digital wallet or even you're saying
like listen what's up
also you again need to like put a
fingerprint or enter the booth so first
we booth that that is very important
secondly please keep one thing in mind
maximum frauds are happening when you're
when you're expecting to receive money
but you're and you're entering the UK
pin in order to receive the money you
don't have to enter a UPF in you enter
the UPI pin
only when you send it so that it so that
is something you need to take care of
all the other activity remember that
lastly don't have room in yeah II
comfortable this is one app because you
know how it really works you know just
because you're getting a twenty rupees
cash back offer from now now some both
app doesn't mean that you know you
switch to backup and even if you have to
means learn it well as when
you know just do a drizzle with somebody
okay like you know this and you want to
pee and when you send me one doing this
just see how it works so that you don't
get confused that you know because it's
a new app now all together so you
shouldn't just get confused and lose
your money so these are the things
that's all some things but you just need
to be very very careful even in your
contacts when you have saved the
particular person you know one digit
going from here to there and you might
just end up paying somebody else so and
even in terms of QR codes also like you
know there used to be a time I remember
you know there's already a QR code and
somebody would miss you missed put
another QR code and the person but the
shopkeeper would involve you know you
would say okay can I just can and pay
and the shop people would say yeah go
ahead and you can and say okay look I
said I'm going by and you would go the
money has actually gone somebody else
who pasted the newer thing so the things
I would I do wanna ask you which is your
favorite UPI your app but I will
obviously ask your other question
relating the same thing you mentioned
right now when you say you know people
shifting from one another and that's the
new digital India we have seen right now
and then firebase cash back in a country
like India madness big thing so I I know
how people shift from you know x-rays I
do our name this app on this open
platform but of course they moved from X
to Y to Z because the initial plan that
they give is really catchy you know a
hundred its cash back or to Andrews cash
back so what is your suggestion to
people who shift apps based on the
profit that getting from those apps so
so you know I would say a maximum of the
plans like you know I have God or my
friends in my community I've got these
are the people who are educated you know
you would expect these frauds happening
with drivers and watch man and you know
people who don't understand technology
and all I think they're much smarter
its maximum happening with the educated
why because I think um they're you know
be educated if not I'll be overconfident
about certain things
you okay not happen to me today if you
are wrong most of the crimes I would say
99% of the times are happy with the
educators law so just for the pie will
be others tend to be I don't think so it
may
Modi as more deformed I mean more
teasing
knowingly about your devices because all
apps need access to let's say maybe or
Kennedy or contact your stories or
whatever from one company already has it
not the second company also has heard of
me we don't know where the mole is or
who has that kind of information to do
some sort of Tyria with you
I think chances and we are any we're
talking about lesser and lesser number
of apps so why are we going to convince
it not absolutely I like how you put
this across that you know what it's the
the ones were educated they are the ones
in the trap most often then the ones who
are actually not that highly educated
and it's a true fact is people to us
right now my next question is coming
from someone called Raj he's asking is
the data on phone the content in the
gallery etc secure no it's not
Wow the only reason I mean when you
install an app you're just you're just
saying that okay the absence I need
permission to your gallery and like or
Instagram or whatever it has access to
your gallery you are backing it up on
the time on to the show world so
obviously as I told you if somebody
wants to like really misuse it for
example let's say if I come across with
an app and I give it to my team members
that look here to any of you needy could
install it you know I am the owner and I
have taken access to the gallery so I
know what all I have and that's the
reason why do we say why do you think
sextortion
is on the rise because a lot of our
intimate movements are stored on the
stored in the gallery so please
understand that nothing is in that one
dumb device would you call that a smart
phone it's all over it's everywhere so
everybody was watching there if you have
that anything that you hiding in that
phone you think it's your private thing
I don't think so I think it's out there
everybody is got the details for it so
make sure you delete them completely or
make sure you never record that to be in
the safe side I have
questioner talk about the gallery as
well the pitch of people have video
calls on different platform what several
start from whatsapp how safe is whatsapp
video coins I think you know as long as
you know we are talking sensible things
we are displaying sensible things as
long as you know I'm not having like you
know it's a virtual medium it's a
cyberspace anything can happen
okay and all the past hacks and we just
have shown that's how bad it's gotten go
whether it is like a Sony hack or you
know whether it was Ashley Madison hack
okay it can't like really go crazy so
here is where you really need to have
that kind of sense that any sense of the
thing I don't have it on my phone like
this is your debit card credit card it
could be obscene things so when he when
I'm making a whatsapp call now what I am
using it for if it is just a casual
conversation that's what if any sort of
training whatever you and I are doing is
absolutely fine why is this doing
anything else on it so nothing is
actually saved it just that we we come
across everything is safe before I kind
of ask you next question because it's
not delivered the questions regarding
the debit and credit card
it was additionally inside about the
place chantara and this bunch of dude
that came across fooling a lot of
Indians with fake calls and made so much
money
there's also serious Outernet fix about
the same thing and that's why I'm coming
to this question right now how to
protect or what proportion should one
take while using debit card or credit
card so we'll break it into two parts
the John Tara thing any such call coming
telling you that look you know your
points are expiring whether they call
you whether they send you a message or
you get an email or whatever it is the
complete weed no the call of the bank
call center you know you call it you
hang up and you got to call of the call
centers and aunt in discuss what is the
issue or as such so no no talking to
anyone as far as these things
and most of the times I've seen people
get defrauded it was the only reason
because they are like in a hurry or
they're all stressed and all hold on
just hang on for that time you know if
it's blocked how does it matter it just
block this way for two hours more when
you're silent I mean you know when
you're just relax go back and call up
the call center now the second part of
the question how do we take care of the
credit and debit you know we always have
this misconception that okay even if
somebody has my CV what can you do the
OTP comes to me know please understand
that is many many foreign countries on
many international websites
I mean ecommerce websites they don't ask
for the OTP right just now that they
have started doing you remember Netflix
also know how it used to happen it's
just now that I see the varieties from
India then they redirected to your bank
otherwise was earlier so I could use
that all the time a lot of course are
happening so please understand this one
thing that as far as your credit or
debit cards are concerned they you know
they can be misused because firstly in
the dark web itself okay
many Indian banks debit and credit cards
are already out over there which means
they have a 16 digit number expiry date
are names and the CVB okay so what you
need to do now you just can't ask your
bank right in this particular position
or in this particular environment right
now to block a card and send them a new
one but what you can do is please
disable the international transaction
you know or just keep it to the minimum
like so for example my certain amount of
money goes to Google but I know it
doesn't move me on thousand rupees what
I have done is I have just you know kept
the limit of 2000 for an international
transaction so even if across the once
you try attend and do something you know
the maximum we can take is two thousand
rupees so this is what we really need to
do even as far as your domestic
transactions are concerned because the
line by and large they give you like a
limit of assisi lakhs nowadays okay but
you don't need that much kind of thing
so what do you need what do you need to
do over there in your domestic
transaction there are all the banks like
you know providing lot any filters
or conditions I was excited that what
you want to do so you can always select
you okay in a day not more than 5,000 or
10,000 or my domain or please reduce my
limit it's 3 lakhs fine thank you so
much but I would want to keep it only to
25000 rupees then I want to shop
something more than that I will just go
in hand final event so you know
controlling your limit it's something
very important and disable the
International one if you're not you
think of that not I'm so glad you
mentioning this point of having a limit
especially while you're traveling
international cause it's it's come
across in my scenario as well where you
don't get to know how much is spending
in different country big base or the
currency difference you have and happen
to spend so much money it's only when
you come back to India realize oh my god
1 lakh rupees has spent over a half like
a baby so glad you mentioned the point
I'm gonna just go back to a1 no question
that is coming in my mind right now
about the safety in the calls and the
apps and so many things so do you agree
that you know before 2001 while we
having phones - not smartphones the
phones and having simple life was much
safer life tonight then trend scenario
oh well I wouldn't say that because you
know what it's made things up and we
need this imagine today in this logged
on if you have that kind of phone what
you would have been doing the way or of
course the great thing you would have
been doing would be like reading book
which we don't but then still there are
people who read on the internet and on
so it's all about how how then in that
case you should see your way also
missing it's all about how well how
smartly I'm using my device so you know
you know you just please understand you
know you you call this as a bank in your
pocket but when you go to the bank with
so much of cash don't you go with so
much of like you know pick partials and
then you know you're like protected
because you've got so much of money with
you the same thing you really need to do
with this this is
a lot of acting can come out and it can
be music misuse also how smartly modern
smartly wisely and you're using this and
then awareness is very important so you
really need kind of a manual now you
know a manual or digital wellness before
I hand over things to you it's as good
as like let's say you know if today you
wanted to interview somebody to
netbanking somebody who's older like a
father or uncle you know who knows
nothing about it wouldn't you be
straining him he'll look you don't give
the password out over there we need to
understand more what is phishing and all
that same thing needs to be done when we
are find any device or we are
downloading an app or doing anything
with technology you know in the last 30
minutes
I'm store that beginning comment that
most of the people are deleting apps on
the phone already things they know about
it and be honest you have unlimited ABS
in my phone as well even to do with the
UPI or a banking a very limited apps
because it's not because I want to keep
so many here because I didn't I choose
not and I think the first thing you
should do with that you choose not to
have to do neat things and creates a
mess and you start becoming safer by
your own means because somebody else
keeps you safe I'm not get into some
digital question social media questions
because a lot of cyber security crime
comes into picture in social media where
there's people talking about against
somebody and for somebody how do you
monitor these things on social media or
if they should be uses give us a little
insight about it
well I don't want to talk so I think
social media is all about really so so
it would be the agencies that would be
monitoring but definitely not me and you
know I want to come back to your app
because you said you have limited apps
and many people might be who are
deleting the app you also need to
understand one thing
go back to your phone go to the settings
and go to the for missions over there
and please remove the permission like
for example an app a food delivery app
my
not me though it doesn't require
permission to your gallery right I mean
you know when you order our food you
don't to show that you were eating the
food okay so please disable that this
has revoked that particular permission
so go through your app setting and you
will like you know you will you will be
like shocked to know the to many of your
apps are having like permissions to the
cameras to the microphone please revoke
it if you have a question you know you
might want to say that you look but then
those apps might not function no just
try it out it will function it's not
that it's not going to function it will
function and if it refuses to function
uninstall it you know we got so many
options nowadays I totally agree so good
you mentioned about it so go back to
those apps liquid settings there is a
wave of revoking your settings making
sure that you are limited giving the
limited access to your phone and that is
one step of being saving your memory to
yourself and not single one out there
I'm sure today many of the people must
feel like buying and thinking of the
actions they were done or by the means
of calls and videos and pictures and I
don't know what more what not any
message that they said you want to give
to people going ahead in future what
they should keep in mind in terms of the
video calls of or calls by the means of
Internet
here you answered it you said keep in
mind and that's exactly what they need
to do so keep the password in mind keep
everything in mind don't don't put
everything on your phone you know don't
put your passwords on the phone put keep
it in your mind it it's easy to remember
I love funny person hashtag whatever
those two now put that also on the phone
don't put your credit card and
everything don't don't store your entire
banya on your phone okay so it starts
your brains are anyway started shrinking
of course the digital era so don't
shrink it further give it some exercise
please I I would take get back to paying
people start memorizing things something
like you know things like those are
extremely extremely or empower
we need to bring back our photographic
memory in our brain I I love the way you
just put across this thought that regain
the memory that you used to have before
while you didn't you didn't need a map
to take you to a place or you didn't
need a nap to buy things for you
you always make sure you put on a piece
of paper and that's how the whole the
life has been going around so I think
the old school is still the best cool to
be in where you can be saved and is
exactly what wish has given to us and
this one quick question to all the youth
who's watching us right now
there was a latest big a spam about the
house party app that that went out loud
most of the people who are watching were
youth live and Facebook and Instagram
across the portal want to know about how
safe is it can they go back and
reinstall the house party app or it's a
big no-no what do you think Ben does
just go ahead install it but don't do
those things you know like okay like
let's say four friends coming together
or a friend coming together and come on
let like Iran do something that's again
something I've seen or TV don't do that
you never know what can happen you know
some people out of excitement want to
take a screen shot or you know there are
like five layers Mallory's on your
phones also with taking screenshots of
your phone just imagine if it hands up
lines up in wrong hand just don't
experiment all this I know it's virtual
world it's a cyberspace but still it's
not safe right now so there if you ever
do anything do it in limited space don't
jump this face and that's when the
problems come in and you also mentioned
that two parallel worlds that will right
now on one is the world we're in and
other words virtual world so make sure
you are equally balanced equally know
where you stand with your foot in and we
don't put your foot in just make sure
you are in the reality of life and being
there that's the best way out thank you
so much at a spot here for join Esther
day I am sure all of you so they have
made sure that they will buy a notebook
or
back tomorrow I append tomorrow start
writing start memorizing things that
have to because that's the way you can
remember things and it's big no-no to
keeping a screenshot of your of your
bank card number or database PIN number
whatever throw all that out of your
phone this the only fool you have make
sure it's all stored here thank you for
joining us here at the Wellness room and
I am sure I have so many other questions
on ask you but time is a concern here so
thank you joining us here it tastes
lovely having you I'm hoping you're safe
when you are happy and positive at home
and I'm sure you have so many books that
is placed behind you and you are making
the most of those books these days
belongs to my son he's making the most
of it in fact I think he's writing one
now oh wow that's very very good news I
hope it's a bus cybersecurity and
keeping list knock mother is in the same
thing the father also in the same that's
the right way said you can always ask
anybody choose the right path and then
they have the old right to say that
another very good messages you just gave
right now and everyone there if they
mature they have the own path to walk
towards thank you again for giving us a
beautiful inside of wellness and where
it actually starts from it starts from
the safety and security of what you are
and how you keep them because that's
what wellness means here and I think
exactly what we're doing
thank you so much at this party or what
no time for joining us it was not having
you with us here and wellness 368 oh
alright so that was measure with a
Sparta giving a three insight about how
you should take care of everything that
you do while doing digital transactions
while if you credit card debit card or
by storing pictures video calls messages
these numerous apps make sure you filter
it make sure you reduce it make sure to
keep your phone limited to apps and
that's the best way to be safe I know
you want all those apps but trust me
there was a time you didn't need all
this app so turn it down
make the most of it go to settings new
book settings when you do not give the
access to the app to make sure they have
all the rights to get into your phone
and stop it right there at wellness 360
at home brought to you by Isis in
numbered our message is to make sure you
are at perfect in every aspect and I'm
sure today again you learn how you can
be perfect just to start with the
wellness thank you so much again for
joining us my name is Luther no path
yeah I will see you next episode
meanwhile what you do is make sure you
are happy make sure you're positive and
make sure you are having a great time
with family and being well all the time
thank you again
you